<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Novel on Absence</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Novel on Absence</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/novel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The hazy Morning light woke me from my empty slumber.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I opened my eyes, and looked around. I was on the island, on solid ground once more. I let myself breathe deeply and truly relax for the first time in a long while. Deep inside of me, I felt a strange sensation of both loss and fulfillment. I soon realised that I was not having to fight for control of my mind anymore. I was free - free of the fragment that had live in me for so many years and influenced my mind. I could truly be myself now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The stairs had slowly gotten more and more derelict as we had arrived at the second floor. As we stepped onto the little platform that marked the floor, I questioned myself as to whether they had been this derelict when I had ascended them before, but the answer came back a resounding no. The tree was decaying, and so therefore so were the stairs that were made out of it. The same holographic insects made their way through the stairs, and I paid no attention to them, knowing that my steps would do them no harm, and that they likely did not even truly exist. They seemed too monotonous, too devoid of any life-giving properties to actually exist, somewhat like the Witches. I wondered to myself if the Witches had created them in the the only way they knew how - through thinking them up, creating them out of pure thought and reason and logic, no ambiguities, perfectly efficient at their singular duty. I wondered how they managed to break through and degrade the otherwise very physical tree were standing in, though the only answers I was able to come up with made me feel uncertain and lost, and I reserved them for a time when I could sit and think. This was not the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 23</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I felt every second move past me as we sailed across. Hawthorn knew the art of sailing better than the rest us, and so she carefully tilted the sail this way and that as we made out way across the lake. The water seemed less dangerous now, and I felt slightly more safe as we moved across the otherwise still water. At night, the boat stopped, because the wind had died down, and Bloodroot and Hejj began to row with two long, skewer like paddles, which moved the boat along relatively slowly. It was achingly slow. The progress we were making seemed as if it would be meaningless unless we got Foxglove and the children back safely. If we did not, I would never let myself live happily, knowing that my hubris is what led to their being taken. Hawthorn came up to me in the night, before we were all to go to sleep on the deck, the cold not bothering us, and gave me a small salve ground out of Sew Root, which she said would help my hands make a speedy recovery.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Sew root?&amp;rdquo; I asked. I had never heard of the plant before, and just hearing its name led ot pangs of grief and regret returning to flood my mind, which I fought to keep off. I had to stay focused on the current problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 22</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once I opened my eyes again, I looked around me to see that I was finally back on the island. I looked up at the ladder, in its pseudo-organic majesty, and the sky, still beholden by a dark grey cloud that made me feel feelings of nausea and aversion. I was on my back, and everything hurt. it felt like my insides were being poured out of me, my entrails lining the area around me  - I must have sustained quite the fall from the ladder I assumed  - but I could see no visible marks of injuy on my body. I tried to get up, but failed terribly, it was as if my bones had turned to liquid, and my will into something hopeless and dejected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 21</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I looked around, or what must have been around, for I had no reference point to check it against.&#xA;I could not tell how much time had passed, my mind and body just floating independent of each other it seemed, aimless. I soon forgot my name, and I did not want to remember it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of a sudden the Witch around me began to darken in colour, become more corporeal, though never actually getting quite close enough to having a physical form for me to dismiss it being in actuality something I had thought up. Nothing happened for a moment, as the world stood still and I waited, not expectant nor bored, in a liminality of emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 20</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once I got to the bottom of the staircase, I ran as fast as I could towards the ladder, which I could see just poking out from under the clouds, th blood stain was still there and I was strangely thankful for it allowing me to wayfind in this otherwise featureless void of ice and cold.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I strapped both of the children onto my back, and began to climb down the ladder as quickly as I could. Soon, I began to see Foxglove, and I felt a wave of relief. The ground spelled safety, and we would try to get to somewhere safe as soon as I arrived. I had decided that I would ask Foxglove to take the children, while I would wait to get answers. The witches had to answer - I would try and make sure they did. I could not be left with no answers after I had spent so much time and so much effort trying to find out. They were the ones that took me, and they would need to have the answers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 19</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ladder was made of a slimy transparent material.&#xA;It rose up into the low lying clouds, ascending at such a steep incline and with such vivacity that I immediately began to wonder of the consequences of slipping off of it at the point it plunged into the clouds above my head. I went up to it, and touched it. Wet. It had a thin layer of some sort of mucus-like film over all of it. I wanted to work out wht it was made of, but I did not want to dead breaking any bit of it, as I soon realised that I would inevitable need to climb up it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 18</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I soon came to myself fully, and wondered how Foxglove had managed to get away from the creature, while I had not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Foxglove, I thought you could not swim.&amp;rdquo; I asked, trying not to sound demeaning.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t. I hid beneath the boat when it had been upturned, and when the creature came to me, it tried to grab me by my waist, but suddenly swam away. It must have been the pouch. Are you sure you did not swallow any water?&amp;rdquo; She replied, looking over at the sun rising, and the birds singing their mournful songs. I thought about it for a second, and realised that the snails in her pouch must have been the things that deterred whatever the creature was. I realised that it could not have been Foxglove who I had seen being taken under the water.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 17</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We continued taking turns rowing throughout the day, until night fell, and we were looking as if we were roughly halfway across the lake. The island looked both larger and smaller than we had initially expected, possible because of its strange rectilinear shape. It came to me in one of those long hours of rowing that the island was quite obviously not natural at all, and had been built by some sort of being. Nature did not like straight lines.&#xA;I assumed that the witches, with their strange ways of thinking and self-ascribed higher thinking led them to choosing such an unnatural shape for their abode. I wondered where the witches lived, because the island was largely sparse and empty. The fog tht had clouded the island before was only thicker as we got close to it, and I sometimes doubted whether it was even there, as the fog often made it seem as if it was a mirage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 16</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I collapsed into a crumple of tears and confusion, my legs giving way to the hard certainty of the ground below my feet. Foxglove rushed over to me, and started trying to speak to me, though I only heard a slurry of noises painted in concern. My vision was the same, seeming to me as if I was looking through a piece of seaglass into a world tainted with red. I felt exhausted, and could not stand up, no matter how much I tried, Foxglove dragged me to a tree near us, and began trying to get my attention, to talk to me. My headache was gone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 15</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once our minds had settled, Foxglove went over to the cage in the side of the area to try and find out a bit more about what was going on in this tent.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I need to know what they want from us. Fa Raven seems to be some sort of ancient being, but the rest of these animals? most of them are from species allied with the Conglomerate, so I need to make sure that they aren&amp;rsquo;t thinking about selling us out.&amp;rdquo; She walked over to the cage, in which there were two foxes and a stoat. Most of the Stoat&amp;rsquo;s left leg had been horrendously burned away, and I could barely stand to look at it. the foxes were not much better, with no major injuries, but having a strange personality that made me feel as if they knew more about myself than I did.&#xA;I let Foxglove take the lead, as I was still thinking about what I had just found out. I was foolishly trying to regain a sense of self, any that I had previously had having been ripped to shreds by the revelation just awarded to me by Fa Raven. I tried to sense the fragment inside of me, trying to isolate its influence in my mind, as if cupping my hand around a section of a lake to keep the water from leaving - I just could not. The influence of thw witches tainted me, I hated myself and I did not want to hurt anybody else because of what I was being led to do. I could not even trust my own thoughts, never really knowing what was me and what was the construct of some understandable mind of a different sort. Not being able to trust yourself instills a different sort of loneliness, where even lies you tell yourself to ease the pain only drive it into you deeper, and you try to stop existing as a conscious entity.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Hey, Stuvlok. Come here.&amp;rdquo; Foxglove called for me. I walked over, trying to avoid squishing any of the small rodents and birds under my feet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 14</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I did not know what to say, so I laughed.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;You cannot be serious?&amp;rdquo; I asked, quickly suppressing any further laughter that I could have expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am blind,&amp;rdquo; The raven stated, as grave as ever, &amp;ldquo;but I am not stupid. I am definitely not a liar.&amp;rdquo; Fa Raven looked at me with a dour expression on their beak, the crack only making what they said viscerally real. Despite all of this, I could not possibly believe any of this. I was not able to physically make myself believe it, even if I wanted to (which I quite obviously did not) and was left searching for the words to ask&amp;hellip; or question&amp;hellip; or accept what had just been told to me. Foxglove spoke up before I had the chance to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 13</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_13/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we came closer an closer to the lake, I began to notice that it seemed almost as if the things that were following us around grew larger in number, the sound of their scurrying and the sheer destruction they left behind in their way growing increasingly greater and greater as the seconds flowed past, and we came closer to the lake.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we ran, I asked Foxglove whether she knew anything about these rodents.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Why are they following us? Do they work for the conglomerate?&amp;rdquo; I asked, expecting her to say that they did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 12</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ground very quickly became very sparse. Whereas previously, the ground beneath my feet had ben smothered in an assemblage of dead leaves and twisting vines, it was now dry and cracked, with barely any plants being able to be seen on its surface. It was not noticeable at first, but I soon came to understand that it was because of the hundreds of feet that must have been hitting the ground constantly, killing off any hope for life that the ground may have had. Foxglove soon told me that she believed that it was neccesary to air on the side of caution now, especially was we were approaching the conglomerate&amp;rsquo;s territory, and that the border was very likely being guarded now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we walked, Foxglove began to tell me what she had been told by Nettle. Apparently, he did not quite trust me as much as maybe I had hoped, and so had told the most crucial information of all to her, once had learnt that he could not accompany us on our journey, at least for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Foxglove seemed giddy with excitement, and I wondered whether she really understood the gravity of what we were about to do. I did not want to be with someone who did not.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I trust you, Stuvlok.&amp;rdquo; She said. I was slightly taken aback.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Why? What have I done to win it? and what would trust help with, if anything?&amp;rdquo; I asked, quizzical in my voice and perplexed at why she had brought this up.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Well, trust is important in a team. Is it not where you are from? You have done nothing to win it, but trust is given to everything, until you see it betrayed, at which point you should give it no more. As long as the being you give your trust to does nothing to break it, they can have it.&amp;rdquo; She said, suddenly assuming a much more philosophical and serious personality. The words she had told me sounded starkly different from her usual chatter, and I doubted that they were her own. The otters seemed to operate on a wholly different set of moral values than I had ever seen before, and it was intensely interesting. During the evenings, when I was alone, I noted these things down, ready to be analysed another day. &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s what nettle told me,&amp;rdquo; she said, back to her usual self, &amp;ldquo;But I doubt it.&amp;rdquo; she stopped for a moment and thought carefully about her next words &amp;ldquo;I think that you can tell whether somebody is trustworthy or not based on how honest you can see them being. I do not think that your body shows me any lies, and so I trust you. How does your trust work?&amp;rdquo; she asked. I thought about whether my body may have been speaking for me during any of the times I had met with the otters, who now, in retrospect, did seem to be analysing my body as much as they had been analysing my speech. I decided to tell her the truth. I could not afford to risk breaking the trust she had on me. Instead of weighing me down, the trust seemed like celestial strings, hoisting me higher and further away from the heady baseness of selfishness. It felt good. &amp;ldquo;Where I used to work, in the town, Trust was earned, never given at first, but earned, and always based on action and gifts.&amp;rdquo; I told her, ruminating on whether any of my teammates had ever really trusted me, and whether I had ever trusted anybody in the guild at all. I soon found myself drifting off into memories again, the woods sombre silences only heightening the feeling of drifting through  place where past and present are one, where stories are reality and reality sounds like a fable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 10</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once the chatter died down, I waited for the inevitable explanation that I needed to better grasp and understand what had just happened. I was desperate for any information hat could tell me more about myself, and had nothing else to really live for anymore other than learning more about myself, and saving Wea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The old otter, who I was told was named Moonwort, spoke again, &amp;ldquo;We shall have to start from before any of this Witch business got started to fully explain what we need you to help us with.&amp;rdquo; He paused for a moment to make sure that I understood, and then went on with his tale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 9</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I heard the river gurgling. I woke. I opened my eyes to see that I was inside of the clearing. Famished, I looked around for any food, unhopeful that I would find any, and if I did, whether I would even be allowed to eat it. There was nobody in the clearing, and I was half thankful, half disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I soon found that somebody had laid a chunk of roasted fish by my feet, in a plate made of a leaf moulded to hold food. I forgot about all of the pains that ravaged my body, all of the fears I had carried and any anxieties that Had carried me so far, and gorged myself on the fish. Though it was unseasoned, I tasted every beautiful note of aquatic brilliance the fish presented me with, I was able to savour the grilled and charred outside, and the fleshy and supple centre, I picked out the bones and shoved them in my pocket. with nothing else, these would serve well as a make-shift defence if any danger were to befall me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By the next evening, I had run out of food.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had managed to exhaust all of my rations, even somehow extending them to one and a half times the length of time that they were originally intended for. I had been carefully controlling what I was allowed to have each day, and had been forcing myself to walk through the stomach cramps and fatigue that hunger brought. I soon found that even with my dedicated attempts, all food was really and truly gone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The woods began to get progressively less and less dense, as if they were gradually shedding their outer coat and allowing their insides to air much more thoroughly. I thought I had seen larger creatures around me as well, but they always seemed just out of sight, and it always happened either at dawn or at dusk, so these crepuscular beings may have just been figments of dreams that did not want to leave my mind as I was waking. At one point, I even noticed that the trees seemed to have changed, and were both squatter and larger-leafed than the trees I had encountered before. Every so often, I would get the chance to slow down and carefully examine the leaves, and I would see that each tree had its own signature of sorts, a seal of identity in its leaves, and this made the leaves seem much more personal to me, and left me daydreaming about the stories I had heard as a child, and imagining myself thinking about talking to the trees as those who were here before us had done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I made my way closer to where my eyes had been drawn, I soon came to realise that it was a clearing of sorts. It was so almost perfectly circular, that for a moment, it almost looked artificial, but the small defects made me realise that must have been natural, likely cleared by some sort of large animal for mating rituals. As I walked closer, I found that the clearing was surrounded by bushes, all of the same species and type. They were also all in fruit. Each bush had hundreds of little purple berries gracing almost every stem and ever woody branch. The berries looked almost a homologous purple from a distance, but when I plucked one of them off and examined them closer, I saw that they were in fact mottled with a few different shades of purple, I crushed one in my hand. A deep-crimson juice flowed out, and the berry emitted a stink so close to the odour of rotting meat that I for a moment looked around me for any sign of a rotting carcass. I dared not taste the berried, both due to the smell and my recent experiences with the water. I doubted that it would end well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I walked for hours. I walked for so long that I no longer remembered when I had started, I had forgotten to take any sort of time-keeping apparatus with me, though I felt a strange sensation that I would very likely not need it where I was going. The woods seemed dead, largely, and I only ever saw a few hares or a deer or two on my journey. I had brought my notebook with me, and so I tried to map the forest where I went, though It was hard keeping the scale correct when I was walking at different speeds, and often found myself falling into daydreams, leaving my body to walk freely among the trees while my mind was someplace else.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The next day, my entire body ached.&#xA;I went to live with my friend Derr, who was now a blacksmith. his house was large enough for all of us to live together, and  - though I rarely found the strength to speak to him or his family, especially about what had just happened - not too far from where my home used to be and where the burnt remains still were.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the night in a bush. It was cold, and not at all pleasant, but I managed to keep the gloom away from me by thinking of all the great things that I would do once I returned to my village. My village was called Fhal, and nobody really knew much about its history. I remember being told tall tales by the older children back when I was young about the origin of the village. I soon learnt to disregard the dragons and kings, and acccept that it was veyr likely started by some goatherds, or pig farmers or somone otherwise just as ordinary and inunique as that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once I got to my hovel, I realised that I needed to find out what the key was for. The symbol on the box told me that it must b something rather valuable, and so I made sure not to tell the two other thieves I shared the hovel with about it. I had never trusted them, and any mone I made was ultimately going to end up paying for my debts to them.&#xA;I made sure to keep the key on me at all times, and hid the box by burying it underground.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/chapter_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Very certain sort of absence filled me as I stood alone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I could not really explain it. It almost ate away at my insides, leaving an emptiness no words of mine could ever hope to fully describe. I tried to use the pain it gave me to my advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I stood above the city, dangling from a spire of a building that reached up into the sky, so high that when I first saw it, I believed that it would anger the gods, showing off the audacity of the mortals beneath them to reach up so high, pierce the clouds and touch the gods.&#xA;I have gotten use to it.&#xA;In that moment, however, I was focused on on thing. The large, ostentatious house I looked onto. The family crest of a dragon intertwined with a dagger told me that it belonged to Welk, the man they called the king of thieves - he had started the thieves guild, and took it over when his companions mysteriously died. No thief dared question him. No thief dared anger him.&#xA;Apparently, other than me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/novel/00_prologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/novel/00_prologue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Woods squirmed with movement every time my lamp&amp;rsquo;s light disturbed the sensitive quiet of the night. The trees stood, cast in deep shadows, looking like bearded giants. My footsteps sounded loud, and cavernous, and vulnerable. The Woods make no noises. The shaved crystal over my eyes kept fogging up, but I did not wipe the beads of moisture away, for fear of missing something around me. Millipedes scurried around my feet - huge ones - two or three qubits long and the thickness of strong sailing rope. I had been walking for hours, I began at sundown, at the edge of The Woods, with my traveller&amp;rsquo;s satchel, lamp and sling pressed close to my body. It was hot then, the day&amp;rsquo;s sunlight had warmed the ground. It had rained the day before. When night fell, it got very cold, very quickly. It was the night of the Eten Dance - a new moon. I normally never missed the festival, yet, today, I had. My leather boots let in water every time I stepped in a puddle or stumbled into a bromeliad. The ground was soft, mushy in strange ways I could not quite understand. It seemed to change consistency, shift often, play with your thoughts. The Woods at night are a dangerous place. My flame was dying, so I added in some more oil, and coaxed the flame awake again. I could not let that flame die. I had decided on my forest trip more or less on a whim, drawn by some strange attraction I had developed over the last few weeks. My mind wandered while I walked. I thought of the dancing that would be happening in the village, the food, the drink, the people. I thought of the dark allure the woods has always posed to me, deep inside my stomach somewhere was the Lodestone that The Woods attracted. It had always been there. Twigs do not snap under my feet, the rains have softened the once strong wood of the trees, and left the bits of the giants for the fungi to clear up. My legs have become tense and it hurts if I bend them too much. I looked around for a while, and found a small cluster of boulders, dry and protected, in a small clearing in the forest. I sat down. I took off my boots and saw the blisters on my feet. I dried my feet off with a patch of moss, and left them out in the air for a while. The rocks are cold. They snatch the heat away from me, and leave me with a slow, viscous cold that takes its time creeping to my core, and will take its time creeping back out again. I took a sip of some tea I had in a small pouch in my satchel. It was not warm, and only gave me more of the same vegetal greenness that The Woods had imbued into me in the hours that it had had its grasp on me. I had entered through its mouth, lured in like an inquisitive calf, walked down The Wood&amp;rsquo;s gullet, slowly getting deeper, and deeper, and deeper, into the abyss of The Woods. The hours I had spent in The Forest had been melding into a grey hum that lived in the back of my mind. Each tree looked the same, I had been forgotten by the rest of the world, I understood know. As I stumbled along, wholly lost, I entered further into the entrails of this great beast that eats all that enter it. The Woods lies there, silent, mocking me, laughing. It laughs at my stupidity, my hubris. I thought I could conquer it, me: a small, useless thing, tiny to the trees, tiny to The Woods. I was incomprehensibly worthless to The Woods - it did not care, It was immortal, It was Everything. Its air kept me alive, it made me blind. It Laughs at me, still.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
