<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prose on Absence</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/prose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prose on Absence</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:54:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/prose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:54:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Woods squirmed with movement every time my lamp&amp;rsquo;s light disturbed the sensitive quiet of the night. The trees stood, cast in deep shadows, looking like bearded giants. My footsteps sounded loud, and cavernous, and vulnerable. The Woods make no noises. The shaved crystal over my eyes kept fogging up, but I did not wipe the beads of moisture away, for fear of missing something around me. Millipedes scurried around my feet - huge ones - two or three qubits long and the thickness of strong sailing rope. I had been walking for hours, I began at sundown, at the edge of The Woods, with my traveller&amp;rsquo;s satchel, lamp and sling pressed close to my body. It was hot then, the day&amp;rsquo;s sunlight had warmed the ground. It had rained the day before. When night fell, it got very cold, very quickly. It was the night of the Eten Dance - a new moon. I normally never missed the festival, yet, today, I had. My leather boots let in water every time I stepped in a puddle or stumbled into a bromeliad. The ground was soft, mushy in strange ways I could not quite understand. It seemed to change consistency, shift often, play with your thoughts. The Woods at night are a dangerous place. My flame was dying, so I added in some more oil, and coaxed the flame awake again. I could not let that flame die. I had decided on my forest trip more or less on a whim, drawn by some strange attraction I had developed over the last few weeks. My mind wandered while I walked. I thought of the dancing that would be happening in the village, the food, the drink, the people. I thought of the dark allure the woods has always posed to me, deep inside my stomach somewhere was the Lodestone that The Woods attracted. It had always been there. Twigs do not snap under my feet, the rains have softened the once strong wood of the trees, and left the bits of the giants for the fungi to clear up. My legs have become tense and it hurts if I bend them too much. I looked around for a while, and found a small cluster of boulders, dry and protected, in a small clearing in the forest. I sat down. I took off my boots and saw the blisters on my feet. I dried my feet off with a patch of moss, and left them out in the air for a while. The rocks are cold. They snatch the heat away from me, and leave me with a slow, viscous cold that takes its time creeping to my core, and will take its time creeping back out again. I took a sip of some tea I had in a small pouch in my satchel. It was not warm, and only gave me more of the same vegetal greenness that The Woods had imbued into me in the hours that it had had its grasp on me. I had entered through its mouth, lured in like an inquisitive calf, walked down The Wood&amp;rsquo;s gullet, slowly getting deeper, and deeper, and deeper, into the abyss of The Woods. The hours I had spent in The Forest had been melding into a grey hum that lived in the back of my mind. Each tree looked the same, I had been forgotten by the rest of the world, I understood know. As I stumbled along, wholly lost, I entered further into the entrails of this great beast that eats all that enter it. The Woods lies there, silent, mocking me, laughing. It laughs at my stupidity, my hubris. I thought I could conquer it, me: a small, useless thing, tiny to the trees, tiny to The Woods. I was incomprehensibly worthless to The Woods - it did not care, It was immortal, It was Everything. Its air kept me alive, it made me blind. It Laughs at me, still.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
